All right!
Satomura & Yao
Hinase & Hananoi
Nice one, Satomi-san!
I just got lucky.
Have you been practicing or something?
No way!
It's our turn next. Let's go for it, okay?
Hananoi-kun, have you been bowling before?
Yeah, a few times.
And you, Hotako?
I've been a few times too.
But I always throw gutter balls.
Aw, you'll do fine.
Satomura & Yao
Hinase & Hananoi
I'm sorry.
Relax, relax.
I did it!
Hota-chan, Hota-chan!
This is so much fun!
Episode 11
Our First Campus Expedition
I haven't hung out with anyone
like this since I moved to Tokyo!
To tell you the truth, I haven't made
a lot of friends in college.
People get creeped out when I bring up
my hobbies, so I'm never sure what to talk about.
But I've always wanted to go out
and let loose like this!
So thanks for inviting me today.
I-I actually always really enjoy talking
to you, Satomura-san. It's so fun!
Hota-chan! You're the cutest
coworker I've ever had!
I guess that makes another one.
That next! Let's do that!
When the sign appears,
hit the drum with these sticks.
We shouldn't just stand here watching.
Wanna play something together?
Nah.
Oh, don't say that.
Besides, I need to talk to you
about something.
We're playing ping-pong at an arcade?
Just one game.
If I win, you have to tell
Hotako all about your past.
So that's the reason he
forced me to come today.
I said you should tell her if you want.
You know, man, I really don't get you.
Whenever Hotako's not around,
you act like a total jerk towards me.
Aren't you worried I might
tell her about that?
Or do you actually want me to?
And "I can tell her if I want"?
Don't try to put that on me.
She wouldn't want to hear something
so important about you from someone else.
If I win, you're never
gonna bring it up again.
We did it!
I'm so sorry. I was holding you back.
No way! I've never gone to an arcade
with friends before. This is super fun.
Hey, two really hot guys are
playing ping-pong together!
Let's go watch.
Yeah!
Huh?
You're pretty good!
Wanna play with Hotako
and Satomi after this?
You're still saying "Hotako this,
Hotako that." Shut the hell up.
Whoa!
Didn't she tell you
to stop calling her that?
She said I could take my time
making the switch.
That she knows how hard it is
to start calling someone a different name.
Yes!
Why the hell are you always sticking
your nose into everything?
Yeah, I can see why it
might bother you. Sorry.
But I've been friends with
Hotako for a long time.
I just don't want to see
her get hurt, you know?
You don't want to see her get hurt, huh?
Hananoi-kun? Yao-kun?
Hotako... Oh!
Game over. I win.
Hey! That wasn't fair at all.
You don't want to see her hurt?
You're the last person I
want to hear that from.
Were you guys competing?
I wish I could've seen it!
All right, we have to get to work soon.
Have a nice shift!
I wonder what he and Yao-kun
were talking about.
What do you want to do now?
Hmm...
Wha—
Hotaru-chan?
Ow, ow, ow.
Sorry if it stings a little.
Oh, I can do that—
I'll take care of it.
I want to do it.
Hananoi-kun, did you have fun today?
Yeah, I did.
It's nice to go out like that sometimes.
Hotaru-chan, you seemed all right today.
Huh?
You told me before that things
are weird between you and Yao.
I started to wonder if something happened.
U-Um, remember when I told you
about the friend who cut my hair?
As a matter of fact,
the boy she liked was Yao-kun.
So I still get a little
scared when I'm with him.
It must be awful to have someone
be so awkward around you
when you've done nothing wrong.
Yao-kun is really nice, so he tries
to pretend like it doesn't bother him.
I finally realized that recently.
So I thought today would be
the perfect opportunity.
I'm glad I looked normal.
I guess that explains it.
Wait, were you worried about me?
No, it's something else. It's not about you,
Hotaru-chan. It's a personal problem.
She wouldn't want to hear something
so important about you from someone else.
You really are amazing, Hotaru-chan.
You put other people's
feelings before your own.
You keep growing as a person.
Hananoi-kun?
But I still need to get stronger.
What do I have to do
to get a clear head again?
Maybe the sooner...
I make you completely mine,
the sooner I'll be able to relax.
That was close.
I almost broke the promise I made to you.
One day,
when we finally share a real kiss,
I want you to be as elated as I will be.
I'm sorry. I put you in an
awkward position again.
I'm such an idiot. I keep doing this to you.
No, that isn't it.
I don't think that's why I just did that.
This has happened a bunch of times before.
My body just moves on its own...
But I can't really put that
feeling into words yet.
Um, Hananoi-kun?
Hotaru-chan.
Listen, I...
There's something I haven't told you yet.
A spring-exclusive cafeteria delicacy
This sells out in seconds every year.
I want to try it,
but I doubt I'll get a chance.
Well, the third-years do have an advantage
in terms of proximity.
I went through the same thing
in middle school.
Huh?
Your middle school had a cafeteria?
Yeah. I lived in the dorms.
Y-You lived in a dorm?!
Sorry again. I still haven't told
you much about my past, have I?
That's okay.
I should have asked sooner
but was holding back.
Is it all right if I ask a little more?
Of course! That's what we promised.
That's right. We decided to embark
on another new endeavor.
Listen, I...
There's something I haven't told you yet.
In truth, I—
W-Wait! Is this something
I really need to hear?
I mean, the way you look right now,
Hananoi-kun... I don't know.
You look like it's the end
of the world or something.
Oh... Sorry.
I guess just got a little nervous...
Well, then can you give me the gist
of what this is about?
Th-The gist of it?
Yeah, yeah!
Um, actually, it's about how
lame I used to be.
I mean, I couldn't blame you
if it made you hate me.
Wait, it's one of those?
In that case, you don't need
to force yourself to tell me.
But I feel like I really should...
There are lots of things you don't know
about me that might make you hate me, too.
Tons and tons of them.
I know we're going out, but it's still
going to be hard to tell each other
every last secret about ourselves.
But you told me about Yao, Hotaru-chan.
Well, I wanted you to know about that.
Hmm, but okay.
Maybe there are things I should tell
you even if I don't want to.
This is kinda difficult.
Oh, I know!
How about we start asking more of the
questions we have about each other instead?
Huh? Of course that's fine with me.
I tend to forget, but we've only officially been going out for two months!
I mean, there are still a whole lot of
things we don't know about each other yet!
So, okay, why don't we start
with the little stuff
and practice talking about
ourselves more and more?
Bit by bit, you know? L-Like beginners,
since that's what we are.
Let's start off easy.
Huh.
So you had to clean and do
your own laundry in the dorm?
Oh, Hotaru?
What a surprise seeing you here.
Shibamu, are you with your club?
Yeah, we're taking a break.
Shibamu is in the kendo club.
What are you two up to?
Um, I was planning to hang
out with Hananoi-kun today,
but it's really pouring outside,
so I guess we're on a campus
expedition until it stops.
Sounds like you're having fun.
Shibamura-san, we're about to start again.
Oh, right.
I'll see you later.
Wait, Hozumi-sensei? I didn't know
he was the kendo club advisor.
What extracurriculars did you do
in middle school, Hananoi-kun?
Track and field.
Wow! So you like running?
I was really weak when I was a kid.
I wanted to get in better shape.
I see.
Oh! Kyo-chan!
Hmm?
Hotaru? What's up?
Well, actually...
Over here!
Go center!
Oh, wow!
Yeah. Pretty cool, huh?
I wish I could come watch him every day.
Oh? Hey, you two! And Hibiki!
Who?
It's that famous second-year kid.
He's in my class.
But you're making your girl
wait on you again?
Must be nice having a girlfriend.
You have someone to comfort
you after a hard workout.
So, what's up? Planning on joining the team?
You're so tall, Hananoi, we'd love to ha—
You should get back to it.
Even his classmates think he's a dork!
Hilarious!
You got me. He always
gives me the cold shoulder.
See you later.
Oh, and sorry, Hibiki. I'm gonna be late,
so you should go on home.
Sure.
I never see him like this in class...
Kei-chan actually has it pretty tough.
In his first year, he jumped ahead
and became a regular player.
He has trouble getting along
with his older teammates.
So thank you, Hananoi-kun.
If he'd kept on blabbing,
they would've teased him even more.
I didn't do a thing.
I didn't really expect that.
I guess Kuratani has his own problems.
I get the feeling that Hananoi-kun doesn't
really hate Keigo-kun after all.
Um, Hananoi-kun, has it always been your
policy to avoid making friends?
No. I had some until middle school.
Oh, really?
But there was only one
I was really close with.
Only one?!
Wh-What were they like?
Hmm...
Maybe that's something he
doesn't want to talk about.
He was a lot older than me.
Oh, the friend you just mentioned?
Yeah.
I was really rebellious in middle school.
When I said I wanted to get my
ears pierced, he helped me out.
Huh?
If a middle schooler said that,
most people would try to stop them.
But he was a free spirit
and didn't care much about stuff like that.
But then he left without saying a word.
I never saw him again.
Maybe that made him so sad,
he didn't want any more friends.
That's a possibility...
I don't want to go through that again.
In that moment, Hananoi-kun looked
so much more tranquil than usual.
And to my surprise, after that, he was
happy to keep talking about his friend.
He didn't strike me at all like someone
who didn't care about making friends.
Hananoi-kun?
Hmm?
You make it sound like
you're a bad person sometimes,
but I don't think that's true at all.
Oh...
You might not realize it,
but I think you're a lot more sincere and
a much better person than you realize.
Listen, I really so want to learn more
and more about you, Hananoi-kun.
I'd be lying if I said I wasn't
curious about the old you.
But the Hananoi-kun I like is
the one with me right now.
If you'd really rather not get into the past,
I don't want to force you to tell me.
S-Sincere?
Uh-huh.
Also, Hananoi-kun,
I think you're really cute!
C-Cute?!
Oh, this is a good chance!
There's something I want to make sure of.
Um...
Would mind closing your eyes
and holding as still as a jizo statue?!
Uh...
Wh-Whenever you hold me and stuff,
my mind goes blank and I completely
lose track of my feelings.
F-For once, I want you to let me
try something like that on you!
Something like that...?
Don't worry. It's just for confirmation.
A-All right.
But to be honest, I don't know...
Depending on the circumstances,
I'm not sure I'll be able to hold back.
I might not be able to stop
myself like I have until now.
Th-That's all right!
I'm ready for it this time.
I'm so sorry. I've kept you waiting
until I knew what I was feeling.
Thank you.
Just holding her hand...
Just touching her...
Just touching him...
It makes me feel so...
Oh, sorry!
I-It's okay. You just surprised me.
I really do think Hananoi-kun is cute.
These are my true feelings
welling up inside me.
You're so cute! I like you so much!
I want to touch you more.
I want to get closer to you.
Hota—
Th-That does it!
Thank you very much for your cooperation!
What was that?
A... A signal...
After the pouring rain cleared,
when the school fell silent
after class had ended...
On this very unusual day,
I had my very first kiss.